{
  "jokes": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "question": "To replace programmers with robots, clients will have to accurately describe what they want.",
      "answer": "We are safe!"
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "question": "A guy ordered a pizza with cheese, olives, onion and red pepper. On getting it, the guy shouted - It is not baked.",
      "answer": "Delivery guy - You only get what you ask for."
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "question": "If somebody refers me for a job",
      "answer": "Will it be considered 'pass by reference' or 'pass by value'?"
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "question": "Once C++ walks into a bar and sees C. C is drunk, falling on the floor, spitting and swearing.",
      "answer": "How classless! -says C++"
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "question": "Are you a RESTful API?",
      "answer": "Because you GET my attention, PUT some love, POST the cutest smile, and DELETE my bad day"
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "question": "I used to know a joke about Java",
      "answer": "But I run out of memory."
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "question": "Why do Front-End Developers eat lunch alone?",
      "answer": "Because, they don't know how to join tables."
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "question": "How do you declare war in JavaScript?",
      "answer": "var war;"
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "question": "Knock knock",
      "answer": "Unsynchronized block\nWho's there?"
    },
    {
      "id": 10,
      "question": "Knock knock. Who's there?",
      "answer": "Very... long... pause...\nJava."
    },
    {
      "id": 11,
      "question": "How many types of people are there in the world?",
      "answer": "There are 10 types of people in the world: those who understand binary, and those who don't."
    },
    {
      "id": 12,
      "question": "What happens when a UDP package walks into a bar?",
      "answer": "A walks UDP package into bar."
    },
    {
      "id": 13,
      "question": "I would tell you a joke about UDP",
      "answer": "But I don't know if you will get it. Either way, I don't care."
    },
    {
      "id": 14,
      "question": "What happens when a SQL query goes into a bar?",
      "answer": "It walks up to two tables and asks, 'Can I join you?'"
    },
    {
      "id": 15,
      "question": "Why does a programmer put two glasses on his bedside table before going to sleep?",
      "answer": "A full one, in case he gets thirsty, and an empty one, in case he doesn't."
    },
    {
      "id": 16,
      "question": "How do you style the Leaning Tower of Pisa in CSS?",
      "answer": "pisa-tower { font-style: italic; }"
    },
    {
      "id": 17,
      "question": "Two bytes meet. The first byte asks, 'Are you ill?'",
      "answer": "The second byte replies, 'No, just feeling a bit off.'"
    },
    {
      "id": 18,
      "question": "How much US bandwidth is used by Netflix?",
      "answer": "1/3 of US bandwidth is used by Netflix. The rest is used by `rm -rf node_modules && npm install`"
    },
    {
      "id": 19,
      "question": "What is debugging?",
      "answer": "Being the detective in a crime movie where you are also the murderer."
    },
    {
      "id": 20,
      "question": "What's behind every good program?",
      "answer": "A frustrated programmer."
    },
    {
      "id": 21,
      "question": "What's it like being a programmer watching someone HACK a computer on TV?",
      "answer": "It's like being a nurse and watching someone in the movie take blood with a carrot."
    },
    {
      "id": 22,
      "question": "Programmer 1: We have a problem!",
      "answer": "Programmer 2: Let's use RegEx!\nProgrammer 1: Now we have two problems."
    },
    {
      "id": 23,
      "question": "Why did my girlfriend dump me?",
      "answer": "After I named a class after her, she felt I treated her like an object."
    },
    {
      "id": 24,
      "question": "What's the programmer's workflow?",
      "answer": "Trying to fix the problem I created when I tried to fix the problems I created when I tried to fix the problems I created when there was a problem"
    },
    {
      "id": 25,
      "question": "A programmer's wife asks: 'Would you go to the shop and pick up a loaf of bread? And if they have eggs, get a dozen.'",
      "answer": "The programmer returns home with 12 loaves of bread. 'They had eggs.'"
    },
    {
      "id": 26,
      "question": "What's your address?",
      "answer": "Developer: 173.168.15.10\nLayman: No man. Your local address\nDeveloper: 127.0.0.1\nLayman: I mean your physical address\nDeveloper: 29.01.38.62.31.58"
    },
    {
      "id": 27,
      "question": "Boy: I like you, do you want to be my GF?",
      "answer": "Girl: ... (30 seconds)\nBoy: Why are you quiet?\nGirl: ... (30 seconds). '504 Gateway Timeout'"
    },
    {
      "id": 28,
      "question": "What are pointers in C like?",
      "answer": "I know a guy who knows a guy... who knows another guy"
    },
    {
      "id": 29,
      "question": "Two strings walk into a bar. What happens?",
      "answer": "The first string says, 'I think I'll have a beer quag fulk boorg jdk^CjfdLk jk3s d#f67howe%^U r89nvy\\~~owmc63^Dz x.xvcu'\nThe second string says, 'Please excuse my friend, He isn't null-terminated.'"
    },
    {
      "id": 30,
      "question": "What do the new MacBook and a black hole have in common?",
      "answer": "There's no Escape!"
    },
    {
      "id": "67e18c53-68de-4c47-839c-b23e533c9662",
      "question": "hello",
      "answer": "NEW JOKE"
    }
  ]
}